Portfolio UP013
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Portfolio
1982 -- 1993
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Observer
Tufts Daily
UP013
0.5 Linear Feet
1 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of issues of the Portfolio which was a student publication originally distributed by the Observer and Daily under the title of the Tufts Magazine from 1982-1985. It evolved into a literary magazine that included poetry and other creative writing. The Portfolio ceased publication in 1993.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts Daily, founded in 1980, is the daily undergraduate student newspaper for Tufts University. Its mission is to provide a source of news for the Tufts community, a forum for the exchange of ideas, and a means for students to gain experience in journalism. It covers university news, sports, and events as well as some national and international news. It also includes editorials, a calendar of events, and syndicated comics. Published and distributed free of charge on class days during the academic year, the Tufts Daily is student-run and receives no financial support from Tufts University. Particularly valuable are the Tufts Daily photographs documenting campus life - the people, places, events, and activities of Tufts University.
- Portfolio, 1982 -- 1993; UP013.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Portfolio, a student literary publication. Portfolio was a student publication originally distributed by the Observer and Daily called Tufts Magazine from 1982-85; it evolved into a literary magazine that included poetry and other creative writing.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts Magazine, 1982-10; UP013.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, 1982-12; UP013.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, 1983-03; UP013.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, 1983-05; UP013.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 1983; UP013.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 1983; UP013.001.001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 1984; UP013.001.001.00007 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 1984; UP013.001.001.00008 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 1984; UP013.001.001.00009 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 1985; UP013.001.001.00010 (Box Volume 1)
  - Portfolio, 1985 -- 1986; UP013.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Portfolio, 1986; UP013.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Portfolio, 1987; UP013.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Portfolio, 1988; UP013.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Portfolio, 1989; UP013.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Portfolio, 1990; UP013.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Portfolio, 1992; UP013.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Portfolio, 1993; UP013.001.002.00008 (Box 2)